<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Indian Curry</title>
    <link href="https://indian-curry.github.io//news/feeds/atom.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://indian-curry.github.io/" />
    <id>https://indian-curry.github.io//news/feeds/atom.xml</id>
    <author>
        <name>Indian curry</name>
        <email></email>
    </author>
    <updated>2017-02-15T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <entry>
    <title>Announcing the formation of Indian Curry.</title>
    <link href="https://indian-curry.github.io//news/posts/2017-02-15-Announcing-Indian-Curry/index.html" />
    <id>https://indian-curry.github.io//news/posts/2017-02-15-Announcing-Indian-Curry/index.html</id>
    <published>2017-02-15T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2017-02-15T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Functional programming has been around since the beginning of computer science. Despite its immense advantages, it has remained largely obscure and relegated to a small community. Recently, functional programming is seeing a new renaissance. The academic community is seeing an explosion of activities, and many more commercial organisations are embracing the functional programming paradigm.</p>
<p>We are a group of functional programming enthusiasts who believe that functional programming holds a lot of potential for Indian institutions and that there is need for a more concerted effort to promote functional programming in both the industry and the academic institutions of India.</p>
<p>Our aim is to:</p>
<ol style="list-style-type: decimal">
<li><p>Improve the collaboration between the various functional programming communities in India.</p></li>
<li><p>Encourage the adoption of functional programming and related formal techniques in the Indian industry.</p></li>
<li><p>Build a functional programming eco-system within the country by enabling closer cooperation between the industry and academia.</p></li>
</ol>
<p>We encourage others to join us in our pursuit of these goals.</p>
<h2 id="join-us.">Join us.</h2>
<p>For discussions join our mailing list <a href="http://groups.google.com/forum/#!forum/indiancurry">indiancurry@googlegroups.com</a>.</p>
<p>Some of of us hang out at <strong>##indian-curry</strong> on <a href="http://webchat.freenode.net/">freenode</a>.</p>]]></summary>
</entry>

</feed>
